There is nothing more deadly than a target turned hunter.
The Weapon is a action film directed by Tony Schiena.
Dallas is a one-man killing machine on a mysterious rampage.
His attacks on biker gangs and meth labs anger the Vegas mob
boss who’s holding Dallas’ girlfriend hostage.
But who is Dallas working for?
Even torture won’t make him talk, and he won’t stop until justice is served.
Dallas, played by Tony Schiena.
Iris, played by AnnaLynne McCord.
Antano, played by Sean Patrick Flanery.
Vinny, played by Jack Kesy.
Blue, played by Cuba Gooding Jr..
Doris, played by Bruce Dern.
The Weapon is a 2023 American action thriller film directed by Tony Schiena, and starring
Schiena, AnnaLynne McCord, Sean Patrick Flanery, Jack Kesy, Cuba Gooding Jr.
and Bruce Dern.